{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622903","name":"Woodward Avenue Market LLC","address":"500 Woodward Avenue Ste 175","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Matthew Jonna","licenseNumber":"237719","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.04494,42.33006","geojson":{"id":"51622903","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.044944209,42.330062857]},"properties":{"name":"Woodward Avenue Market LLC","owner":"Matthew Jonna","address":"500 Woodward Avenue Ste 175","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"237719","establishmentid":"51622903","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"3/22/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3919","name":"Sterling Services Comerica ODC","address":"500 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5092","name":"Townhouse Detroit Ste. 200","address":"500 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622740","name":"BESA","address":"600 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1322","name":"Grand Trunk Pub","address":"608-612 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4131","name":"Woodward Coney Restaurant, Inc.","address":"616 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"3194","name":"Bangkok Crossing: Thai Restaurant","address":"620 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4886","name":"Subway","address":"660 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5407","name":"Shake Shack Michigan LLC ","address":"660 Woodward Ave Ste. 5A","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5088","name":"Central Bar & Grill LLC","address":"660 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4157","name":"Lunchtime Global","address":"660 Woodward Ave #110","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"50522","inspectionDate":"2020-01-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"8-103.12","violationDescription":"If the REGULATORY AUTHORITY grants a VARIANCE as specified in  § 8-103.10, or a HACCP PLAN is otherwise required as specified under § 8-201.13, the PERMIT HOLDER shall:\r\n(A) Comply with the HACCP PLANs and procedures that are submitted as specified under § 8-201.14 and APPROVED as a basis for the modification or waiver; and\r\n(B) Maintain and provide to the REGULATORY AUTHORITY, upon request, records specified under ¶¶ 8-201.14(D) and (E) that demonstrate that the following are routinely employed;\r\n(1) Procedures for monitoring the CRITICAL CONTROL POINTS,\r\n(2) Monitoring of the CRITICAL CONTROL POINTS,\r\n(3) Verification of the effectiveness of the operation or process, and\r\n(4) Necessary corrective actions if there is failure at a CRITICAL CONTROL POINT.","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"SUSHI BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"DISPLAY COUNTER","subLocation":"In the Display","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-01-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment slicer","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Prep table","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-01-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-01-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make easily accessible."},{"violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"At the Bulk food bins","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING ROOM","subLocation":"On top of the Dishwasher (high temperature)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING ROOM","subLocation":"Under the Dishwasher (high temperature)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"In standing water","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"On the Counter(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2020-01-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"48120","inspectionDate":"2019-06-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"wall(s)","subItem":"wall covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"Wall(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-402.12","violationDescription":"Unless otherwise approved, floor-mounted EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be SEALED to the floor or elevated on legs that provide at least a 6 inch clearance between the floor and the EQUIPMENT (COUNTER-MOUNTED equipment that is not easily moveable shall be elevated on legs at least 4 inches high).\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor-mounted equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to floor","subProblem":"","location":"BUFFET","subLocation":"Floor sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"BUFFET","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-05-29T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622903"}}